question_data = [
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games",
     "type": "boolean",
     "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "The first Maxis game to feature the fictional language &quot;Simlish&quot; was The Sims (2000).",
     "correct_answer": "False",
     "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "In World of Warcraft lore, Thrall is the original wielder of &quot;Doomhammer&quot;.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "Mortal Kombat was almost based on Jean-Claude Van Damme movie.", "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "In Portal, the Companion Cube&#039;s ARE sentient.", "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "In &quot;Super Mario World&quot;, the rhino mini-boss, Reznor, is named after the lead singer of the band &quot;Nine Inch Nails&quot;.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "In &quot;Call Of Duty: World At War&quot;, the first appearance of the &quot;PPSH-41&quot; in &quot;Zombies&quot; was in the map &quot;Der Riese&quot;.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "The scrapped Sonic the Hedgehog 2 level &quot;Hidden Palace Zone&quot; was later reused in the iOS port of the game. ",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "In career mode of &quot;Need for Speed: Underground 2&quot;, the first car the player can drive is the BMW M3 GTR.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "Shang Tsung is a playable character in Mortal Kombat XL.", "correct_answer": "False",
     "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"category": "Entertainment: Video Games", "type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium",
     "question": "The game Garry&#039;s Mod originally took assets and codes from the popular Half Life 2 mod JBmod.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}
]
